<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Vibe LTD - Chocolate, Coffee, and Cannabis Monthly Subscription</title>
    <link>https://vibeltd.co/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Vibe LTD - Chocolate, Coffee, and Cannabis Monthly Subscription</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright> Vibe LTD. All Rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 17 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://vibeltd.co/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://vibeltd.co/account/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vibeltd.co/account/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FREQUENTLY ASKED QUESTIONS</title>
      <link>https://vibeltd.co/frequently-asked-questions/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vibeltd.co/frequently-asked-questions/</guid>
      <description>What if I&amp;rsquo;m allergic to or just don&amp;rsquo;t like either chocolate, cannabis, or coffee? Vibe will offer a &amp;ldquo;2&amp;frasl;3&amp;rdquo; option soon, so you can remove any one item from your provision.
What if I prefer Tea to Coffee? We love Tea too, and will be offering a Tea option very soon.
What if like coffee but only drink decaf? Decaf is awesome! You can specify your preference for decaffeinated coffee beans when you subscribe.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thank You, You&#39;re Confirmed in the Vibe Beta</title>
      <link>https://vibeltd.co/thank-you-confirmation/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vibeltd.co/thank-you-confirmation/</guid>
      <description>Whats next? We will be in touch very soon about reserving your Provision.
Provisions cost $69 (includes shipping) and ship ever month.
Provisions will feature new products each month, all sourced for amazing quality and exceptional flavor.
If you have any questions or feedback please send us an email to hello@vibeltd.co or tweet us : @vibeltd
Thanks so much!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vibe Pre-Launch SignUp</title>
      <link>https://vibeltd.co/prelaunch-signup/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vibeltd.co/prelaunch-signup/</guid>
      <description>Almost finished&amp;hellip;
We need to confirm your email address. To complete the Beta signup process, please click the link in the email we just sent you. Thanks so much!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PRIVACY POLICY</title>
      <link>https://vibeltd.co/privacy-policy/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vibeltd.co/privacy-policy/</guid>
      <description>Last updated September 1, 2017 Vibe LTD (“we” or “us” or “our”) respects the privacy of our users (“user” or “you”). This Privacy Policy explains how we collect, use, disclose, and safeguard your information when you visit our Facebook application (the “Application”). Please read this privacy policy carefully. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE WITH THE TERMS OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY, PLEASE DO NOT ACCESS THE APPLICATION.
We reserve the right to make changes to this Privacy Policy at any time and for any reason.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>